Queen Esther is a drama film directed by John T. Coyle.
A Jewish woman, born as Hadassah but known as Esther, becomes
queen of Persia and thwarts a genocide of her people.
Esther, played by Ottile Kruger.
Zubal, played by Michael Ansara.
Xerxes, played by Charles Evans.
Mordecai, played by Richard Hale.
Scribe, played by Charles Jordan.
Chamberlain, played by Cy Kendall.
Queen Esther: A Story from the Bible is a 1947 American
biblical drama film produced by Reverend James K.
Friedrich and directed by John T.
Starring Ottilie Kruger in the title role, it is the first sound
film adaptation of the Bible's Book of Esther.
The film explores themes of persia, queen, bible,
middle ages (476-1453), biblical.
The tone is emotional.